We have one general in the other world.
So, we want to listen to the general.
As we have God's generals, we have the other people generals.
They are other people.
So, we listen to him. God is in control.
That I mentioned that - we should also get ready for battle now, today.
They will try, but God will see us through.
That that name is mentioned, the satanic kingdom general, they will try but God will see us through.
That is to tell you that really, they are from the other world.
So, it's either they will burn the intelligent lights - they cannot do more than that.
But they cannot burn my mouth and my throat.
Immediately the Prophet said "they will burn the intelligent lights - they cannot do more than that",
all the lights in the church went out.
This is to tell you that really, they are from the other world.
We are fighting a battle, but not against flesh and blood,
against the powers and rulers and principalities of darkness from the other world.
But as the prophet said, God is in control.
As the lights begin to come back on in the church auditorium,
Prophet T.B. Joshua reminds the church of his words. "They cannot burn my throat, my mouth."
Immediately, the lights go out again.
Truly, a prophet is a communicator between the visible and invisible world.
As the prophet said, "that that name is mentioned, the satanic kingdom general, they will try,
but God will see us through. God is in control."
The lights now begin to come on all around the church, as the choir leads the congregation in worship to God
for seeing them through, for victory in Christ Jesus is victory assured.
Jesus, worthy to be praised.
We give You all the glory. We worship You, our Lord. You are worthy to be praised.
Hallelujah! Yes, you are in a prophetic ministry.
And apart from what is happening in our midst, we said it, it happened - but it is not yet over.
Unless we are not touching that area.
But we shall touch it today.
Any moment from now, we are going to listen to the confession of this man, the satanic kingdom general
Professor Chukwudi N. Okakpu, let us listen.
My name is Professor Chuckwudi Nathan Okakpu from Ogbunike, Oyi, in Anambra state.
I'm the arobinagu of Iguedo.
I am an inborn occult wizard
and an inborn Grand Llama of Science Beyond Materials.
known popularly in no less than 74 countries in the world.
I was supposed to be here five years ago.
It took time to know where I'm going.
With all my spiritual research and discoveries…
Two years ago, when I took up the decision,
I made a consultation because I'm an astrologer.
There is no great astrologer in the world that does not know me.
A lot of people in these secret sects and organisations
claim to be astrologers while they are not.
They must be taught by a master.
The popular mystical healers around the world
such as the goddess of India,
then Dr. Agowa Ebeze of New Delhi,
this are the major authorities in the whole of India.
That gives me a compliment as a superior.
You could not be an anti-Christ then and operate without my
endorsement and signature.
I have a lot of people.
Some, I do communicate with them through short time astral manifestations.
I can stay here and appear in any part of Europe.
I can talk to actual person.
They will do what I advise because I operate like a spirit.
Before I took up the decision of being here,
Lucifer told me face to face
that now that I have decided to derail from the usual agreement,
that he is going to kill me.
Anybody that does not serve the true God, Jesus Christ of Nazareth,
that very man that was crucified at the cross of Calvary,
will have no peace.
Yes, from the experience, I have no peace.
There is no atom of peace for 32 years.
I started doing further research to know the solution of peace.
But from my vast experience physically and spiritually,
I discovered that the Sr. Prophet T.B. Joshua is not a material pastor.
I went to receive Jesus Christ as my personal Master and Saviour
and it is today.
I need a deliverance through Sr. Prophet T.B. Joshua.
And consequently, by mere coming here and seeing you, sir,
peace is right now reigning in me.
If you are such a person that patronizes shrines, herbalists,
I am the ultimate.
Why am I here?
To receive Jesus Christ as my Lord and Master
through Sr. Prophet T.B. Joshua.
You are welcome here today.
Thank you.
Watch your screen.
Deliverance in the power of the Holy Spirit.
In the MIGHTY Name of Jesus Christ!
In Jesus Christ name I declare you FREE in Jesus' name!
Well known occult grand master.
Stand up!
All witch doctors, all astrologers, necromancers, palm readers, they all know him, and receive his endorsement.
He had been with lucifer, seeing him face to face,
talked with him, chat with him, carried out his mission.
And he had never received a deliverance that would take him totally from the kingdom of darkness.
In the MIGHTY name of Jesus Christ!
OUT in Jesus Christ name!
All power of principality: OUT, OUT, in Jesus' Christ name.
Watch your screen.
Stand up!
Can you bring that chair here?
Sit down.
Watch your screen.
He is completely under the influence of the Holy Spirit.
A known and respected occult grand master worldwide.
If there is anyone that has witnessed or you were once a member,
please come out.
Having prayed for prof. Chukwudi and delivering him in the power of the Holy Spirit,
T.B. Joshua called those coming for the first time among the congregation,
who had had an encounter with the professor, or had been his follower in the past.
He's my master, sir. I'm one of his followers.
I'm one of his followers. I worked under him for two or three years
before I left him, when I was in the East.
You were one of his followers?
Yes master.
Watch your screen.
The man of God said: anyone present here, who had been a follower should come out.
Deliverance for the master and the follower.
To anyone who had been a follower the man of God said: come out and be delivered.
There is one of the followers
of the prof. Chukwudi N. Okapu.
One of his followers
Here is another one coming forward.
Watch your screen.
Deliverance for the follower.
COME OUT!
Prophet T.B. Joshua, I thank him immensely for bringing me
very close to the True Light.
It is now time for Christ to reign.
Hallelujah
Jesus is alive
Death has lost its victory
And the grave has been denied
Jesus lives forever
He's alive
He's the Alpha and Omega
First and last is He
The curse of sin is broken
We have perfect liberty
The Lamb of God is with us
He's alive
Hallelujah
Jesus is alive
Death has lost its victory
After grave has been denied
Jesus lives forever
He's alive
He's the Alpha and Omega
The first and the last is He
The curse of sin is broken
We have perfect liberty
The Lamb of God is with us
He's alive
You said you were once a follower?
Yes.
I do collect power from one of his followers in Anambra state.
What do you use the power for?
To fight and protect myself.
So, you too, you were once a member?
Yes sir, he was a master to me.
He was using me to do most of his work. Since I left him,
life became so miserable for me.
Fortunately I saw him here and I was surprised.
How are you feeling now, sir?
I feel like a newborn baby.
Any time you pray - remember him in prayer.
The deliverance you received is to send you back to preach the gospel to all your followers.
To bring them back to our Lord Jesus Christ.
To those that believe in me and my lectures about the universe: I am sorry for my past mistakes.
They should also forgive me for deceiving them.
And they should change the way I have changed.
They have to receive deliverance.
Tell the whole world; now you have received a new life - your duty.
I am out to serve God in Spirit and truth because I have been a woeful sinner.
You are tired.
I am tired of sin.
Glory be to God.
Thank you man of God for delivering my uncle.
It is your uncle?
Yes sir.
He says he is sorry for his past life.
Let him eat and rest.
He paid the debt
He did not owe
I owed a debt
I could not pay
I need someone
To wash my sins away
Now I can sing a brand new song
Amazing grace
Lord Jesus paid the debt
That I could never pay.
He paid the debt
He did not owe
I owed a debt
I could not pay
I needed someone
To wash my sins away
Now I can sing a brand new song
Amazing grace
Lord Jesus paid a debt
That I could never pay
Begin to give thanks to God for your deliverance.
What's happened to this man is communicated to you.
Give thanks to God that you witnessed it.
I witnessed it.
Our Lord Jesus Christ is alive.
Can we hear from him again?
You say: Jesus
Jesus is my Lord and personal Saviour from today.
Can you tell us why you decided today to accept Jesus as your Lord and Saviour?
If I cannot receive Jesus Christ then it is orbituary.
He is telling you he is very close to the grave.
They are demanding his life.
And he does not want to die.
Stand up.
Can you tell the world who is Jesus?
He is the truth
the way
and life
Those of you who know what you are using at home, in the village
and you are coming here for the first time, you have inherited something from the witch doctor
please come out.
Come brother.
Watch your screen.
You inherited some charm.
You are welcome sir.
After the deliverance of prof. Chukwudi and his followers
the Spirit of God prompted T.B. Joshua to call on those who had inherited something
from witch doctors, charm users and alike to come forward for deliverance.
You can see them coming out from across the auditorium.
As they respond to the call.
They want to be free.
They want to be redeemed.
We thank God that the gracious calls Jesus gives encourages our hope
that when we come in sincerity and humility we will receive the deliverance we are asking for.
This is yours. Come on.
This is mark. Can you see?
Look at this one too. Here.
That is the mark that she would not go anywhere.
She is always under their eyes.
Come.
It was my friend that took me there.
I didn’t know that the man was like that.
Since that day, me, my parents, everything has scattered.
Stand up.
Follow me. One, two, three.
You know what you did to a lady?
Yes, sir.
You collected her blood.
There are evil spirits inside of me.
There are evil spirits inside of you?
Yes, big.
You initiate people.
Yes.
You have initiated three people.
Inside the water.
Yes.
I want to meet you.
I am taking you on deliverance process.
You are coming here for the first time.
This is why I am approaching you this way.
I am expecting you and I will be in your midst.
This ring is an occultic ring.
Yes, sir.
Come here. Stan up.
So, thank you very much.
After the service, I asked him to go and bring some of the things around
because the deliverance cannot be complete unless we touch his shrine
and the house.
This is prof. Chukwudi Natan Okapu.
The former leading inborn Grand Lama of Science Beyond Materials.
Following the 22nd March 2009 Sunday service at the Synagogue Church of all Nations
acting upon the instruction and righteousness by prophet T.B. Joshua
prof. Okapu is here in his village to collect those mysterious object
associated with his former life in the world of darkness.
This the home base of Professor Chukwudi N. Okapu,
former earth's leading inborn Grand Lama of Science Beyond Materials.
There was an iroko tree (occultic tree) in this very direction.
That is, cassava iroko tree.
That is where our name Okapu, is derived.
That cassava iroko tree happened to be a shrine.
Let’s go to my mystic sensitive place.
This is the mystic sanctum of Professor Chukwudi N. Okapu,
the earth’s leading inborn Grand Lama of Science Beyond Materials.
The sanctum that is just like the one in Tibet.
The one in Tibet is not built by gold
but it is like a forest where the masters reside
for self-realization and awareness.
This house is a part of the sanctum
but it is where I do keep the mysterious snakes
that cannot be seen by the ordinary eyes.
But to my greatest surprise, immediately after my deliverance
through the man of God, Sr. Prophet T.B. Joshua,
while returning home, all the way from Lagos,
I discovered that before my arrival, the snakes had disappeared.
Part of his mystic sanctum this house is where the professor kept his mysterious snakes
which could not be seen by the ordinary eye.
He's stated that after his deliverance at the Synagogue Church of All Nations
and upon his arrival back at home, the snakes had strangely disappeared.
I know that man o I know I know I know
That man gave me peace o
I know I know I know
I know T.B. Joshua I know I know I know
Joshua gave me peace o
This is the mystic sensitive place
of Professor Chukwudi N. Okapu,
the earth’s leading inborn Grand Lama of Science Beyond Materials,
now a born again through The Synagogue Church of All Nations.
A look into to the professor's mystical sensitive place reveals many strange objects.
In my mystic sensitive place, I can entertain over 200 people.
This table signifies love.
Ever before my visit to The Synagogue Church of All Nations,
for the past 17 years
I did not know how to eat because of constant fasting
and astrological dry fasting.
Among the objects arranged around the room, here are two occultic garments he used as
the inborn Grant Lama of Science Beyond Materials.
Praise and thank you Jesus
Praise and thank my Jesus
T.B. Joshua gave me peace o
I know I know I know
T.B. Joshua gave me joy o
That is mine, another set of my mystical wares.
There used to be a magic wand that follows this
but it’s not around now because I gave it out to a king.
The king is late and he transferred it to other people.
This is a vibrate. It represents the Arobinagu Iguedo - meaning the shrine
in the jungle of Iguedo.
This is the lion gown meant for it.
The other ones are the materials that follow it
before handing the magic wand.
The red garment along with the crown and the magic wand, he said were worn together
to form one uniform.
This is the lion gown
and represents the shrine in the jungle of Eguedu.
This is my black garment.
The man that could have put it on before me was
Dr. Agowa Ebeze of India – but he was unable to put it on.
It represents some certain vibrations it the spiritual planets.
Lucifer and the agents of darkness are all aware.
It is this very garment that I used to endorsing even the antichrist.
And you can never perform as a perfect antichrist
without my endorsment.
And I used this very garment in endorsing them
and packaging them to the world.
This black garment was used by prof. Chukwudi in endorsing the antichrist.
The only other person who could have possibly worn the garment was doctor Agowa Ebeze
of New Delhi, India, but he was unable to wear it.
The professor explained that lucifer and agents of darkness are all aware of this garment.
Arranged in his mystical sensitive place are various photographs of prof. Chukwudi N. Okapu
wearing these garments throughout the years.
I know that man i I know I know I know
That man gave me peace o
I know I know I know
I know T.B. Joshua I know I know I know
Joshua gave me peace o
I know I know I know
He healed my sickness
T.B. Joshua gave me joy o
I know I know I know
This is my inner place for astral projection.
This is a small foam.
In astral projection very mighty foam.
This is just to relax your body while trying to demarcate
the inward self from the outward carcass, called the body.
If I want to meditate, I use this seat in meditation.
Then I place an object on the wall while carrying out the meditation.
The professor then takes us to his inner place used for an astral projection.
Laying on the mattress is the purple garment which the professor used for this purpose.
This white chair was used for the meditation.
But I believe that now that I have been called,
there should be total demolition of this mystic base and sensitive place
so that the new structure can be put in place.
There is nothing that Jesus lacks.
After having accepted Jesus Christ as his Lord and personal Saviour at the Synagogue Church of All Nations
the professor stated that this inner place, as well as the mystic sanctum must now be totally destroyed,
so that a new structure can be built, where Jesus Christ is the foundation.
This is my dear mother, my lovely mother,
popularly known as the mother of faith.
She’s a born again member.
She is now 82 years old.
The professor introduced us to his 82 years old mother,
a new-born Christian who today is thanking Jesus Christ for her son's deliverance through T.B Joshua
at the Synagogue Church of all Nations.
My God is a good Lord.
When He sees a person, He knows if they are genuine.
Praise God.
Putting on the garments he once used for destruction professor Okapu rejoices in the Lord,
Showing that the satan and his objects no longer have any power over him.
I know that man o I know I know I know
That man gave me peace o
I know I know I know
I know T.B. Joshua I know I know I know
The man of God o I know
I can now eat o I know I know I know
My tummy is open o
I know I know I know
I know that man o
I know that man o I know I know I know
Help me to thank my Jesus
Praise and thank my Jesus
I know that man o I know I know I know
That man healed my sickness
I know I know I know
Do you understand
that Jesus loves you?
He says go all is well
He’s from time beyond o
What again do you need?
Bretheren - Jesus loves you.
He really loves you.
Do you understand
that Jesus loves you?
Victory obtained through Christ Jesus is victory indeed.
And the rest is history.
Returning from his journey to the village, where T.B. Joshua had sent him to go
and bring back his occultic items and charms, here prof. Chukwudi N. Okapu strides confidently
into the Synagogue Church of all Nations auditorium.
He is wearing one of the occultic garments he once wore as the former earth's leading inborn
Grand Lama of Sciences Beyond Materials.
Let's hear from him.
My name is prof. Chukwudi.
prof. Chukwudi Nathat Okapu
the earth's leading inborn Grand Lama of Science Beyond Material.
Now a born-again in conclusion.
I was in a lifeless state. I was like a dead man.
I couldn’t have seen weeks if I didn’t come to the Synagogue Church.
I couldn’t have seen a week. I was just a minute to my grave.
But, let me tell you;
ever before my coming here, Jesus Christ has been appearing
whenever it is tough with me.
He appeared to me three years ago.
I saw Jesus again appearing in my dreams, that I should
see that man called pastor T.B. Joshua.
Yes.
Let me tell you;
everybody knows my size. Even lucifer knows my size.
Everybody knows my size. The spirits know my size.
I came here. When I saw T.B. Joshua in person,
I said, “I will do some experiments, I will test some powers”.
I will try to know where I am – whether where I am is the right place.
So, as I was sitting down, I decided that the first thing I have to do
as I’m here, is to burn the plant – the generator
so that there will be no light anywhere.
In reference of what prof. Okapu has just said, that during his first visit to the Synagogue Church
of all Nations he had made every attempt to destroy the church power supply
so that there would be no light
Let us take a look at what happened during that service when prof. Okapu sat among the congregation that day.
Please - take a note of T.B. Joshua words.
They will try but God will see us through.
That that name is mentioned, the satanic kingdom general,
they will try but God will see us through.
Moments later all the lights in the Church went out.
YES - I did everything for the plant and the power room to explode
but Jesus ceased it.
I tried again – it was ceased.
And having ceased it two times, after that I was delivered.
Then after that deliverance, the demon disappeared.
Watch your screen.
Deliverance in the power of the Holy Spirit.
In the MIGHTY name of Jesus Christ.
In Jesus's Christ name - I declare you free in Jesus's name
But the elementals in my place, I still had spirits; I had snakes.
For 17 years, I have not eaten.
Can you stand three days or one week without eating?
Seventeen years! I cannot remember when I might have ever sat down and finish a plate of food.
I heard that T.B. Joshua heals – let me be healed too.
My highest problem in life was to eat food.
Now that I have been delivered, I went to eat like every normal human being.
After the explanation, the man of God gave me anointed water in a can.
I looked at it. The water was not even up to half of the can.
I said, “What can this small water do in my body?”
It’s just like brushing my teeth.
I took it. The remaining one, I took it again and went home with it.
I went home with it.
To my greatest surprise, before the Emmanuel TV Team arrived at my place with me,
I discovered that those powers had run away.
I didn’t know that spirits are scared too.
Something like this. See the wonderful water
that made my faith to be even more stronger.
The water that supplied the energy, the water that opened up the stomach.
In my place, I started hearing different types of sounds in my stomach
as if there was a market going on in my stomach.
What does it mean?
Does it mean that this thing will make me purge? I said “It’s a disgrace”.
How can?
There was nothing like purging. The next thing was hunger.
I started looking for food, biting even fruits, vegetables – anything with green leaves.
My aged mother, Mrs. Roseline Nwanbu Okapu, 82 years old, started preparing something for me to eat.
At my place there, I ate seven times.
Since then till now, it’s from six times, seven times to ten times a day that I eat.
For that I have a little statement to make.
But before that I want you to join me in singing that song;
I know that man o I know
I know that man o
I know I know I know
That man gave me water
I know that man o
I know I know I know
That man T.B. Joshua
I know that man o
I know I know I know
That man gave me water
The water made me healthy
I know I know I know
Brethren thank my Jesus
Brethren thank your Jesus
I know I know I know
Help me thank my Jesus
Brethren thank my Jesus
I know I know I know
Brethren thank your Jesus
Brethren thank my Jesus
I know I know I know
Brethren thank your Jesus
I know that man o
I know I know I know
That man T.B. Joshua
Thank you.
Don’t see what is happening here to be an ordinary drama.
There is a confusion in the astral plane.
But lucifer has lost control.
All those human beings living under the sun, that believe in ornamental and rings,
anywhere in the world, that power has been disconnected.
No matter the country, no matter the personality, whoever offered the ring to you -
send it back to the water now, wherever you are around the world.
For those of you in Africa and Nigeria, that had been hypnotized by herbalists and ju-ju priests
know that nothing that any herbalist or ju-ju priest would give to you, or has ever given to you before
will ever function again.
Now all ju-ju priests, all antichrists have to repent, or else they will be disgraced.
Now, I am going to come up. I have other things to tell the world, but I want to sample
some of the materials I came with.
One is the black garment.
Everybody that knows me also knows me with the garment.
This very garment is the garment that I used in endorsing powers, authorities -
satanic authorities and powers
and designing images as God for the earth world dwellers to worship.
I put on this very garment it the sixth planet above, sixth realm above.
That is where I put it on first before putting it on in the physical.
So, this is called “Harbinger’s attire”.
I thought I’m a harbinger. It’s now that I’m a harbinger of Christ and no more a harbinger to lucifer.
This rope represents the 80 titles – all the titles of the earth.
No matter the ceremonies, I had domination over them.
You can see three knots that I designed.
I tied these knots. I tied it one, two, three knots,
meaning that, I have no business with three zeros.
Total disconnection.
I am not a material for Christ and no more a material for lucifer.
Now that the planets are shaking, lucifer has lost his control.
This crown means that I’m the king of the gomes.
In this world today we have two powers on earth.
Two great powers.
Apart from the power of the Holy Spirit, which is that of Christ.
The first set of people of powers are known as the "authoritatives".
The authoritative group of people are those acquire their power
through attachment to higher occult organizations or masters
Some - through gradual development and self-awareness, self-realization.
And some - through any other means.
That is a group known as "authoritatives".
The second group of people is the "extraordinaries", meaning those born and gifted with power.
It is where I belong.
Some of those people are known as the "gomes". Some are scientists, without any physical education.
They were gifted in way one way or the other.
I want to use this opportunity to forgive all my offenders.
I cannot be a good Christian, a born-again without forgiving my enemies.
I do not pray that my enemies would die.
I am not such a Christian.
But they should live and see how the future will look like.
And I’m advising you – truly, if you say you’re a born-again
not that, ‘I believe in Christ’, - I’m a born- again, what about your thinking?
True Christianity starts from the way you think, your mind and your speech.
Everything has to be like a man of God.
Think positive. Talk positive. All that will come out of your mouth should be what will give glory to God.
Those who think evil and they are Christians are those who still suffer witchcraft attack.
After the deliverance, they are suffering evil spirit attack.
Why?
They repented and were delivered through the lips.
Their deliverance did not touch any planet.
You repent without true repentance.
Have you changed?
Changed from every ungodliness to godliness.
Don’t serve two masters at a time.
This is an advice to everyone.
Sit down.
Let me tell you about the pot.
The pot represents some certain vibrations in the planet, meaning that I am positive thinker and mind.
Whatever evil you come with, goes back.
And the pot represents that very function – the force.
The law of reflection.
I put it there so that anybody that thinks evil against me in any form, or in breaking of a kola nut
or through incarnation or invocation, of any form, anywhere in the world -
all those efforts – this thing is a magnetic force – it will collect it.
If you come to my compound in Igbo land and bury any charm, it will appear here.
Now it is empty.
Very very empty.
I have "emptied" it
As you see the pot - I have another one that produces the law of reflection.
Starting from the time somebody remembers to start undoing me or planning evil against me,
it is at the same time that person will start to suffer one thing or the other – torment.
All those things are he’s planning will always go back.
I won’t even know that he’s planning such things.
The pot had given me a sign before now.
One of the leading antichrists became aggressive because he did not want me...
he must have heard that I am now a material for Christ.
Everybody thought that all of us would have remained in faith with lucifer
and died just like that, waiting for the next incarnation.
Thank you. Congratulation.
Can you give some words of encouragement to people all around the world?
Yes – have faith in Jesus Christ. Jesus Christ can never disappoint you.
Stand up and say this.
Have faith. While having faith, you, don’t think evil, or plan any evil.
Your people over there - what is the advice you want to give them?
The advice I’m giving to you – all my former members, all my members
before I became a born-again is:
be a born-again. Join the Synagogue Church of all Nations.
No. Join a living church. This church is not the only living church.
Or any living church of your choice.
You discovered this living church. There are also other living churches.
The Lord just directed you here for your deliverance.
There are other living churches all over the world.
Here is not the only living church.
So, advise them please.
There are many living churches all over the world.
For me, I know I recognise that of…
If you are a true born-again back me up with your nice voice.
I know I know I know
I know that man o
That man T.B. Joshua
I know I know I know
I know that man o
That man T.B. Joshua
I know I know I know
I know that man o
That man gave me water
I know I know I know
I know that man o
That man gave me water
I know I know I know
I know that man o
That man gave me water
I know I know I know
Thank you Lord Jesus Christ for my deliverance,
and I’m praying for more power to worship Him in Spirit and truth.
I am praying for more ability to know the Lord because
I discovered that there is nothing called enjoyment in this world.
Is it beer? Is it alcohol? Is it India hemp? Is it cigarette? Is it cocaine? Is it clubbing in the night? Is it?
Show me that live under the sun, that is too much to be admired.
The rich are tired with all this.
The poor that has no money, when you see them at the roadside - they are happy with 4 bottles of beer.
What about a man that can not be happy with a box of wine worth 25 000 dollars?
Or a hard drug worth million dollars?
He can not be happy.
I discovered – nothing can give you happiness in this world – only peace.
In my former kingdom, I made them to believe that they are all peaceful.
that they have peace – while they are in a burning flame – flame of fire.
When you see the faces of my former members, you will discover that they have no peace.
A peaceful man has no time for criticism, tribalism.
But here – the peace I have never seen before.
How can somebody that has not been able to eat for 17 years be peaceful?
The first day I came here, everywhere there was like a burning fire, because I was angry;
I was not happy: I was flaming up.
Because 1. there was no food in the stomach.
2. I didn’t even know what could even make me to eat from that moment till the next ten years to come.
The past 17 years of "no eating" had led me to that.
And they are telling me stories.
So, I was aggressive.
But today, after my healing, after my deliverance, the stomach opened.
When my stomach opened, I became peaceful.
You can see that I had no weight when I came for the first time.
But now I’m moving fine. I’m stronger.
When you see the recording you can see that I had no strength.
But watch me now.
If there is any policeman, let him come to do some exercise - boxing.
I did my exercise this morning. I jogged as a healthy man.
So now, I’m thanking my Lord Jesus Christ for total deliverance and healing.
I believe in Christ; I will remain a servant of Christ throughout my life.
Hallelujah.
You have listened to the ex-general in the other world.
So, he’s giving thanks to God for the deliverance he has received, and today, Jesus is Lord.
I want to hear from you: Jesus is Lord.
Jesus is Lord.
Glory be to God Almighty.
Thank you.